<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
  <TextBlock>
        <ID>1</ID>
        <LocationA/>
        <Text>RAVA: This is amazing! And, also unsettling. This wasn't here when I first arrived.</Text>
    </TextBlock>
    <TextBlock>
        <ID>2</ID>
        <LocationA/>
        <Text>JAI: I'd love to say it isn't complicated, but it is. I'll spare you the details.</Text>
    </TextBlock>
    <TextBlock>
        <ID>3</ID>
        <LocationA/>
        <Text>RAVA: Oh, please, tell me. I'm curious.</Text>
    </TextBlock>
    <TextBlock>
        <ID>4</ID>
        <LocationA/>
        <Text>JAI: To put it simply, there used to be four accessible dimensions: up-down, left-right, forward-back, and future-past.
         But now we have discovered the next dimension, the 5th spatial dimension.</Text>
    </TextBlock>
    <TextBlock>
        <ID>5</ID>
        <LocationA/>
        <Text> Every object has a 5th-dimensional "shadow." this "shadow" is a near-infinite extension of the object, but we can't normally see it, let alone access it.</Text>
    </TextBlock>
    <TextBlock>
        <ID>6</ID>
        <LocationA/>
        <Text> We have simply moved a few <![CDATA[<i>inches</i>]]> through the 5th dimension. if we mine all this away we just need to go a bit further.</Text>
    </TextBlock>
    <TextBlock>
        <ID>7</ID>
        <LocationA/>
        <Text>RAVA: You mean we're standing exactly where we were, just off by a few inches?</Text>
    </TextBlock>
    <TextBlock>
        <ID>8</ID>
        <LocationA/>
        <Text>JAI: Yes, and in the fifth dimension, although we can't picture it in our minds, we have access to theoretically infinite amounts of metal.</Text>
    </TextBlock>
    <TextBlock>
        <ID>9</ID>
        <LocationA/>
        <Text>RAVA: But how did we move at all?</Text>
    </TextBlock>
    <TextBlock>
        <ID>10</ID>
        <LocationA/>
        <Text>JAI: A fish can't conceive of moving through the air, but with a hook, they travel nonetheless.</Text>
    </TextBlock>
    <TextBlock>
        <ID>11</ID>
        <LocationA/>
        <Text>RAVA: Thats what you're calling it, a hook... That kind of makes sense. Now how do we get out?</Text>
    </TextBlock>
    <ShipLogConditions>
        <RevealFact>
            <Condition>11</Condition>
            <FactID>BB_MINES_REC_FOUND</FactID>
        </RevealFact>
    </ShipLogConditions>
</NomaiObject>